<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Communities on QGIS　WEBサイト</title>
    <link>https://qgis.org/ja/community/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Communities on QGIS　WEBサイト</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>ja-JP</language><atom:link href="https://qgis.org/ja/community/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Brand Guidelines</title>
      <link>https://qgis.org/ja/community/organisation/guidelines/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://qgis.org/ja/community/organisation/guidelines/</guid>
      <description>プロジェクト 概要 スクリーンショット 地図 ケーススタディ プラグイン ビジュアルチェンジログ コミュニティ 参加する 認定プログラム QGIS 財団 Charter 年次総会 年次報告書 財務 プロジェクト組織 インフラストラクチャー ブランドガイドライン Contributor Credits 会合 QGIS 開発者ミーティング Reimbursements for Developer Meetings QGIS ユーザーミーティング メーリングリスト ローカルユーザーグループ メンバーブログ リソース 文書 インストールガイド 検査 ロードマップ レポート OGC Certification パフォーマンス 書籍 サポート FAQ バグ報告 コミュニケーションチャンネル 商用サポート StackExchange セキュリティ QGIS Metrics Plugins Metrics ブログ 資金調達 寄付 寄付者 メンバーシップ メンバー 過去メンバー グッズ ダウンロード アーカイブ QGIS Trademark and brand guidelines ¶ We’re thrilled that you want to refer to either the QGIS project or the QGIS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Certification Programme</title>
      <link>https://qgis.org/ja/community/certification/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://qgis.org/ja/community/certification/</guid>
      <description>プロジェクト 概要 スクリーンショット 地図 ケーススタディ プラグイン ビジュアルチェンジログ コミュニティ 参加する 認定プログラム QGIS 財団 Charter 年次総会 年次報告書 財務 プロジェクト組織 インフラストラクチャー ブランドガイドライン Contributor Credits 会合 QGIS 開発者ミーティング Reimbursements for Developer Meetings QGIS ユーザーミーティング メーリングリスト ローカルユーザーグループ メンバーブログ リソース 文書 インストールガイド 検査 ロードマップ レポート OGC Certification パフォーマンス 書籍 サポート FAQ バグ報告 コミュニケーションチャンネル 商用サポート StackExchange セキュリティ QGIS Metrics Plugins Metrics ブログ 資金調達 寄付 寄付者 メンバーシップ メンバー 過去メンバー グッズ ダウンロード アーカイブ Become a certified trainer ¶ The QGIS Certificate Program is designed to promote both community involvement in the QGIS project and quality education for QGIS software.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contributor Credits</title>
      <link>https://qgis.org/ja/community/organisation/credits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://qgis.org/ja/community/organisation/credits/</guid>
      <description>プロジェクト 概要 スクリーンショット 地図 ケーススタディ プラグイン ビジュアルチェンジログ コミュニティ 参加する 認定プログラム QGIS 財団 Charter 年次総会 年次報告書 財務 プロジェクト組織 インフラストラクチャー ブランドガイドライン Contributor Credits 会合 QGIS 開発者ミーティング Reimbursements for Developer Meetings QGIS ユーザーミーティング メーリングリスト ローカルユーザーグループ メンバーブログ リソース 文書 インストールガイド 検査 ロードマップ レポート OGC Certification パフォーマンス 書籍 サポート FAQ バグ報告 コミュニケーションチャンネル 商用サポート StackExchange セキュリティ QGIS Metrics Plugins Metrics ブログ 資金調達 寄付 寄付者 メンバーシップ メンバー 過去メンバー グッズ ダウンロード アーカイブ Contributor Credits ¶ Individuals, institutions and firms who contributed code to QGIS can let people know about their contribution by:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get involved</title>
      <link>https://qgis.org/ja/community/involve/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://qgis.org/ja/community/involve/</guid>
      <description>プロジェクト 概要 スクリーンショット 地図 ケーススタディ プラグイン ビジュアルチェンジログ コミュニティ 参加する 認定プログラム QGIS 財団 Charter 年次総会 年次報告書 財務 プロジェクト組織 インフラストラクチャー ブランドガイドライン Contributor Credits 会合 QGIS 開発者ミーティング Reimbursements for Developer Meetings QGIS ユーザーミーティング メーリングリスト ローカルユーザーグループ メンバーブログ リソース 文書 インストールガイド 検査 ロードマップ レポート OGC Certification パフォーマンス 書籍 サポート FAQ バグ報告 コミュニケーションチャンネル 商用サポート StackExchange セキュリティ QGIS Metrics Plugins Metrics ブログ 資金調達 寄付 寄付者 メンバーシップ メンバー 過去メンバー グッズ ダウンロード アーカイブ Ways of Contributing ¶ Participate in Support Channels Report Bugs QGIS Documentation Translate QGIS Develop a Plugin Develop QGIS Core Sustain &amp;amp; Donate</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grant Program</title>
      <link>https://qgis.org/ja/community/organisation/grants/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://qgis.org/ja/community/organisation/grants/</guid>
      <description>プロジェクト 概要 スクリーンショット 地図 ケーススタディ プラグイン ビジュアルチェンジログ コミュニティ 参加する 認定プログラム QGIS 財団 Charter 年次総会 年次報告書 財務 プロジェクト組織 インフラストラクチャー ブランドガイドライン Contributor Credits 会合 QGIS 開発者ミーティング Reimbursements for Developer Meetings QGIS ユーザーミーティング メーリングリスト ローカルユーザーグループ メンバーブログ リソース 文書 インストールガイド 検査 ロードマップ レポート OGC Certification パフォーマンス 書籍 サポート FAQ バグ報告 コミュニケーションチャンネル 商用サポート StackExchange セキュリティ QGIS Metrics Plugins Metrics ブログ 資金調達 寄付 寄付者 メンバーシップ メンバー 過去メンバー グッズ ダウンロード アーカイブ Grant Program ¶ ADD CONTENT</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Infrastructure</title>
      <link>https://qgis.org/ja/community/organisation/infrastructure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://qgis.org/ja/community/organisation/infrastructure/</guid>
      <description>プロジェクト 概要 スクリーンショット 地図 ケーススタディ プラグイン ビジュアルチェンジログ コミュニティ 参加する 認定プログラム QGIS 財団 Charter 年次総会 年次報告書 財務 プロジェクト組織 インフラストラクチャー ブランドガイドライン Contributor Credits 会合 QGIS 開発者ミーティング Reimbursements for Developer Meetings QGIS ユーザーミーティング メーリングリスト ローカルユーザーグループ メンバーブログ リソース 文書 インストールガイド 検査 ロードマップ レポート OGC Certification パフォーマンス 書籍 サポート FAQ バグ報告 コミュニケーションチャンネル 商用サポート StackExchange セキュリティ QGIS Metrics Plugins Metrics ブログ 資金調達 寄付 寄付者 メンバーシップ メンバー 過去メンバー グッズ ダウンロード アーカイブ Infrastructure ¶ This page should show you all the infrastructure and services that QGIS uses, and current contacts or owners.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mailing Lists</title>
      <link>https://qgis.org/ja/community/organisation/mailinglists/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://qgis.org/ja/community/organisation/mailinglists/</guid>
      <description>プロジェクト 概要 スクリーンショット 地図 ケーススタディ プラグイン ビジュアルチェンジログ コミュニティ 参加する 認定プログラム QGIS 財団 Charter 年次総会 年次報告書 財務 プロジェクト組織 インフラストラクチャー ブランドガイドライン Contributor Credits 会合 QGIS 開発者ミーティング Reimbursements for Developer Meetings QGIS ユーザーミーティング メーリングリスト ローカルユーザーグループ メンバーブログ リソース 文書 インストールガイド 検査 ロードマップ レポート OGC Certification パフォーマンス 書籍 サポート FAQ バグ報告 コミュニケーションチャンネル 商用サポート StackExchange セキュリティ QGIS Metrics Plugins Metrics ブログ 資金調達 寄付 寄付者 メンバーシップ メンバー 過去メンバー グッズ ダウンロード アーカイブ Mailing Lists ¶ We communicate on mailing lists divided by topics and target groups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meetings</title>
      <link>https://qgis.org/ja/community/organisation/meetings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://qgis.org/ja/community/organisation/meetings/</guid>
      <description>プロジェクト 概要 スクリーンショット 地図 ケーススタディ プラグイン ビジュアルチェンジログ コミュニティ 参加する 認定プログラム QGIS 財団 Charter 年次総会 年次報告書 財務 プロジェクト組織 インフラストラクチャー ブランドガイドライン Contributor Credits 会合 QGIS 開発者ミーティング Reimbursements for Developer Meetings QGIS ユーザーミーティング メーリングリスト ローカルユーザーグループ メンバーブログ リソース 文書 インストールガイド 検査 ロードマップ レポート OGC Certification パフォーマンス 書籍 サポート FAQ バグ報告 コミュニケーションチャンネル 商用サポート StackExchange セキュリティ QGIS Metrics Plugins Metrics ブログ 資金調達 寄付 寄付者 メンバーシップ メンバー 過去メンバー グッズ ダウンロード アーカイブ Meetings ¶ Since 2009 the QGIS community has been organizing developer and user meetings around the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project organisation</title>
      <link>https://qgis.org/ja/community/organisation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://qgis.org/ja/community/organisation/</guid>
      <description>プロジェクト 概要 スクリーンショット 地図 ケーススタディ プラグイン ビジュアルチェンジログ コミュニティ 参加する 認定プログラム QGIS 財団 Charter 年次総会 年次報告書 財務 プロジェクト組織 インフラストラクチャー ブランドガイドライン Contributor Credits 会合 QGIS 開発者ミーティング Reimbursements for Developer Meetings QGIS ユーザーミーティング メーリングリスト ローカルユーザーグループ メンバーブログ リソース 文書 インストールガイド 検査 ロードマップ レポート OGC Certification パフォーマンス 書籍 サポート FAQ バグ報告 コミュニケーションチャンネル 商用サポート StackExchange セキュリティ QGIS Metrics Plugins Metrics ブログ 資金調達 寄付 寄付者 メンバーシップ メンバー 過去メンバー グッズ ダウンロード アーカイブ Who&amp;rsquo;s Who ¶ QGIS as a Project is currently organised as an association legally based in Switzerland with the following structure:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QGIS Developer Meetings</title>
      <link>https://qgis.org/ja/community/organisation/meetings/dev_meetings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://qgis.org/ja/community/organisation/meetings/dev_meetings/</guid>
      <description>プロジェクト 概要 スクリーンショット 地図 ケーススタディ プラグイン ビジュアルチェンジログ コミュニティ 参加する 認定プログラム QGIS 財団 Charter 年次総会 年次報告書 財務 プロジェクト組織 インフラストラクチャー ブランドガイドライン Contributor Credits 会合 QGIS 開発者ミーティング Reimbursements for Developer Meetings QGIS ユーザーミーティング メーリングリスト ローカルユーザーグループ メンバーブログ リソース 文書 インストールガイド 検査 ロードマップ レポート OGC Certification パフォーマンス 書籍 サポート FAQ バグ報告 コミュニケーションチャンネル 商用サポート StackExchange セキュリティ QGIS Metrics Plugins Metrics ブログ 資金調達 寄付 寄付者 メンバーシップ メンバー 過去メンバー グッズ ダウンロード アーカイブ QGIS Developer Meetings ¶ 💁 Do you want to organize a new meeting?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QGIS User Meetings</title>
      <link>https://qgis.org/ja/community/organisation/meetings/user_meetings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://qgis.org/ja/community/organisation/meetings/user_meetings/</guid>
      <description>プロジェクト 概要 スクリーンショット 地図 ケーススタディ プラグイン ビジュアルチェンジログ コミュニティ 参加する 認定プログラム QGIS 財団 Charter 年次総会 年次報告書 財務 プロジェクト組織 インフラストラクチャー ブランドガイドライン Contributor Credits 会合 QGIS 開発者ミーティング Reimbursements for Developer Meetings QGIS ユーザーミーティング メーリングリスト ローカルユーザーグループ メンバーブログ リソース 文書 インストールガイド 検査 ロードマップ レポート OGC Certification パフォーマンス 書籍 サポート FAQ バグ報告 コミュニケーションチャンネル 商用サポート StackExchange セキュリティ QGIS Metrics Plugins Metrics ブログ 資金調達 寄付 寄付者 メンバーシップ メンバー 過去メンバー グッズ ダウンロード アーカイブ QGIS User Meetings ¶ 💁 Do you want to organize a new meeting?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reimbursements for Developer Meetings</title>
      <link>https://qgis.org/ja/community/organisation/meetings/reimbursements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://qgis.org/ja/community/organisation/meetings/reimbursements/</guid>
      <description>プロジェクト 概要 スクリーンショット 地図 ケーススタディ プラグイン ビジュアルチェンジログ コミュニティ 参加する 認定プログラム QGIS 財団 Charter 年次総会 年次報告書 財務 プロジェクト組織 インフラストラクチャー ブランドガイドライン Contributor Credits 会合 QGIS 開発者ミーティング Reimbursements for Developer Meetings QGIS ユーザーミーティング メーリングリスト ローカルユーザーグループ メンバーブログ リソース 文書 インストールガイド 検査 ロードマップ レポート OGC Certification パフォーマンス 書籍 サポート FAQ バグ報告 コミュニケーションチャンネル 商用サポート StackExchange セキュリティ QGIS Metrics Plugins Metrics ブログ 資金調達 寄付 寄付者 メンバーシップ メンバー 過去メンバー グッズ ダウンロード アーカイブ Reimbursements for Developer Meetings ¶ The QGIS project holds twice-yearly developer meetings, typically somewhere in Europe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>User Groups</title>
      <link>https://qgis.org/ja/community/groups/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://qgis.org/ja/community/groups/</guid>
      <description>プロジェクト 概要 スクリーンショット 地図 ケーススタディ プラグイン ビジュアルチェンジログ コミュニティ 参加する 認定プログラム QGIS 財団 Charter 年次総会 年次報告書 財務 プロジェクト組織 インフラストラクチャー ブランドガイドライン Contributor Credits 会合 QGIS 開発者ミーティング Reimbursements for Developer Meetings QGIS ユーザーミーティング メーリングリスト ローカルユーザーグループ メンバーブログ リソース 文書 インストールガイド 検査 ロードマップ レポート OGC Certification パフォーマンス 書籍 サポート FAQ バグ報告 コミュニケーションチャンネル 商用サポート StackExchange セキュリティ QGIS Metrics Plugins Metrics ブログ 資金調達 寄付 寄付者 メンバーシップ メンバー 過去メンバー グッズ ダウンロード アーカイブ User Groups ¶ Current list of QGIS user groups ¶ Registered 2016 or earlier ¶ 🇧🇷 QGIS Brasil (Brazil) Contact: Arthur Nanni 🇩🇰 QGIS Brugergruppe Danmark (Denmark) Contact: Jacob Arpe 🏴󠁧󠁢󠁥󠁮󠁧󠁿 QGIS UK (England) Contact: Simon Miles 🇩🇪 QGIS Anwendergruppe Deutschland (Germany) Contact: Thomas Schüttenberg 🇮🇹 Gruppo degli utenti italiani di QGIS (Italy) Contact: Matteo Ghetta 🇯🇵 QGIS User Group Japan (OSGeo.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
